pubg.com 2019-11-16

# Privacy Policy - PLAYERUNKNOWN'S BATTLEGROUNDS

**Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: 10th of Oct 2019

1\. Introduction  
2\. Who We Are  
3\. Information We Collect  
4\. Cookie and Related Technologies  
5\. How We Use Your Information  
6\. Sharing Your Information  
7\. International Data Transfers  
8\. Retaining and Deleting Personal Information  
9\. Our Policy Concerning Children  
10\. Links and Third Party Services  
11\. Security of Your Information  
12\. Other Agreements That Govern Your Use of The Site  
13\. Your Privacy Rights  
14\. Amendments  
15\. Contact Us

**1\. Introduction**

PUBG CORPORATION and/or its affiliates (“PUBG”, “we”, or “us”) keep and process information about you (“you” or “user”). We comply with all applicable laws related to personal information and strive to protect the rights of individual users by adopting Privacy Policy in accordance with relevant laws and regulations. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal information about you during and after your relationship with us.

**2\. Who We Are**

We provide games (“Game(s)”) and related services, including, without limitation, official site (“Site(s)”), customer service and forum service (Collectively, “Service(s)”).

**3\. Information We Collect**

We collect information about you and the Services you use. Information may also be required to enter into a contract with you or to perform a contract with you (such as to provide Service at your request), and failure to provide any information may result in our inability to provide requested services or products. The information we collect falls into three different categories: 1) Collecting information directly from you; 2) Collecting information automatically; and 3) Information collected from third parties.

1) Collecting information directly from you

You may provide us with the following information when playing our Games and/or Services. Because we offer a variety of Games and Services, the information you provide us may differ in some cases. For example, these include:

– Email address, password, date of birth to create and use PUBG global account

– Email address, password, date of birth, display name to use Forum service

– Email address, Steam account name, nickname, region, gamertag to use customer service

– Email address, name, date of birth, country of residence, nickname, Steam account name, gender to apply for participation in the event, survey, tournament and other events held by us

– Nickname to create a character in-game

2) Collecting information automatically

We automatically collect certain information when you playing our Games and/or Services. The type of information that we automatically collect may vary, but generally includes:

– IP address

– MAC address

– The type of Internet browser or computer operating system

– Domain name of your Internet service provider

– Your browsing behavior while using our Services

– User statistics(e.g. Number of games played, Kill/Death, headshot ratio, game playtime, etc.)

– Information about your computer, device, hardware and operating system

3) Information collected from third parties

When you use our Games and/or Services using a third party platform, such as Steam, Twitch, Xbox Live, PSN or Facebook, we collect certain information from your third party platform’s profile/account as permitted by the terms of the third party platform and your privacy settings thereon. For example, these include:

– Steam: SteamID64, Steam ID, Display Name, Profile Image

– Twitch: Twitch ID, Display name, Email address, User name

– Xbox Live: Xbox ID, Display Name

– PSN: PSN Account ID, Date of birth, Online ID, Region, Sub Account

– Facebook: Name, Profile Image, Email Address, Friends list

**4\. Cookie and Related Technologies**

We use cookies and other technologies to collect demographic information, personalize your experience on the Site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer (if your browser is enabled to accept cookies) to track movements within web sites and to customize your experience within the Site.

Most Internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions or “Help” screen to learn more about how to manage cookies. Please note, however, that if you block cookies, some portions of the Site may not function properly.

We do not control cookies in third party ads, and you are encouraged to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. The ads appearing on the Site may be delivered to you by third-party advertising companies. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We also maintain log files which contain Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. We use log files to monitor traffic on the Site, to report information to our advertisers and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of the Site, we may block certain IP addresses. IP addresses may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Service and any applicable end user license agreement.

Google® Analytics;

More specifically, PUBG may use the following advertising functions of Google® Analytics and collect personal information as provided by Google®, and you may withdraw your consent by deactivating such functions in Google®’s advertising settings: Remarketing by using Google® Analytics; Google® Display Network Exposure Report; Google® Analytics Demographics and interests Report; and Integrated service allowing the collection of data through Google® Analytics by using advertising cookies and anonymous IDs. More information about Google’s own privacy policy can be found at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy>

Sizmek;

Sizmek collects anonymous information from users visiting the website ([https://www.pubg.com](https://www.pubg.com/)). The technologies utilized allow Sizmek to collect this information entirely anonymously and allow us to deliver interest-based advertising. More information about Sizmek’s own privacy policy and how to opt out can be found at[ https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/)

**5\. How We Use Your Information**

We use the collected information for a variety of purposes, primarily, to provide the Service to users and to improve quality of the Service. These include:

– Solve technical problem and improve quality of the Service

– Identification of individual users to provide the Game service

– Technical protection against usage of unauthorized programs

– Preventing inappropriate gameplay that could harm other users

– Provide customer support by collecting and answering inquiries

– Provide forum service on the website

– Provide information on events & surveys and provide opportunities to participate, to provide advertisement and for other marketing and promotion purposes

– Tracking usage patterns and analyzing trends of users, calculate statistics on service use

– Searching user statistics and provision of leaderboard

In the majority of cases, processing of your personal information will be justified on the basis that:

– the processing is necessary to perform a contract with you or take steps to enter into a contract at your request: Most of the time, the reason we process your information is to perform the contract that you have with us. For instance, as you go about using our Service, we use your information to maintain your account and your profile and to provide Service and customer support to you.

– the processing is in our legitimate interests, which are not overridden by your interests and fundamental rights: We may use your information where we have legitimate interests to do so. One of our legitimate interests are to use website user and visitor data to conduct and develop our Service and business activities with them. We may also analyze users’ behavior on our services to continuously improve our Service, we suggest offers we think might interest you, and we process information for administrative, fraud detection and other legal purposes.

– the processing is necessary for us to comply with a relevant legal obligation: For example, we may process your personal information to comply with applicable accounting rules which require keeping accounting records and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement.

– you have consented to the processing: From time to time, we may ask for your consent to use your information for certain specific reasons. You may withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal by contacting us at the address provided in this Privacy Policy.

**6\. Sharing Your Information**

We give permission to third parties, including service providers which process personal information on behalf of us to provide customer support and to manage community. Examples of these third parties include:

– our business partners (for example, in order for them to provide you with discounts or offers that may interest you)

– customer service providers to provide customer support service

– third party program restriction providers to block cheating tools and unauthorized programs

– cloud computing service providers to provide cloud storage services

– payment service providers to assist with payment for transactions or providing withdrawing service for sellers

– marketing platforms and providers of analytics services relating to users’ behavior, in order to tailor the Service

– online survey service providers in order to improve the game service

**7\. International Data Transfers**

We operate globally and transfer your data to countries and other regions where you are located. If your personal information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of personal information.

Additionally, when information transferred from the European Union, we will also take steps to ensure that your information a receives the same level of protection as if it remained within the EU, including by entering into data transfer agreements using the European Commission approved Standard Contractual Clauses, obtain your explicit consent, or by relying on certification schemes such as the EU – US Privacy Shield. You have a right to obtain details of the mechanism under which your information is transferred outside of the EU by contacting [pubg_privacy@pubg.com](mailto:pubg_privacy@pubg.com).

**8\. Retaining and Deleting Personal Information**

In principle, We will remove your personal information without any delay after the purpose of collecting personal information is achieved. Personal information stored as hard copy will be shredded or incinerated, and personal information stored as soft copy will be removed using a technical measures in a way that cannot be reproduced. However we may retain your personal information even after you have closed your account with us or we have ceased providing Services to you, if retention of your personal information is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud, cheating or abuse, or enforce this Privacy Policy or any other agreement we may have with a user.

**9\. Our Policy Concerning Children**

We do not knowingly collect, use or share any personal information about children (generally considered to be under the age of 13 in the U.S., under the age of 16 in Europe or depending on the country where you reside) without verifiable parental consent or as permitted by law. Some of the features on our Games and Sevices are age-gated so that they are not available for use by children. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe your child has provided us with personal information, you can contact us and request your child’s information to be deleted from our system.

**10\. Links and Third Party Services**

If you click on a link to a third party website, including, without limitation, an advertisement, you will leave the Site and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we do not have responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as we do. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to the Site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal Information.

**11\. Security of Your Information**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect information submitted to us, both during transmission and after we receive the information. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on the Site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is completely secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**12\. Other Agreements That Govern Your Use of The Site**

In addition to this Privacy Policy, your rights and obligations concerning the use of the Site are governed by our Terms of Service, any end user license agreement, any other supplemental agreements, and other applicable policies, guidelines, and requirements. When you sign up to use the Site, please review each of the aforementioned agreements carefully, as you must agree to be bound by each of the agreements before you may use the Service.

**13\. Your Privacy Rights**

Subject to limitations in applicable law, you are entitled to object to or request the restriction of processing of your personal information, and to request access to, rectification, erasure, and portability of your own personal information. To make a request concerning your rights or if you have any other question, please contact us by sending an email to the address specified in the “Contact Us” section. We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. In certain countries, including in the EU, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal information. The data protection authority you can lodge a complaint with notably may be that of your habitual residence, where you work or where we are established.

If you are a California resident, you may have these additional rights:

– California residents have the right to receive 1) information identifying any third party company to whom we may have disclosed (within the previous calendar year) his/her personal information for that company’s direct marketing purposes; and 2) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. If you are a California resident and wish to obtain such information, please send a request email to [pubg_privacy@pubg.com](mailto:pubg_privacy@pubg.com).

– California residents under the age of 18 have the right to request removal of any content or information that they have posted on our Site, such as forum or message board. To make such a request, please send an email to [pubg_privacy@pubg.com](mailto:pubg_privacy@pubg.com). Please be aware that the removal of your information or content may not be complete or comprehensive, and residual copies of such removed information or content may remain on our servers. In addition, we are not obligated to remove any posted content or information that has been copied or reposted by a third party, that has been rendered anonymous, or that we are required to keep by law.

**14\. Amendments**

We may amend, at our discretion, any portion of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting or displaying the amended Privacy Policy on our Site. We will provide notice on our Site or by other appropriate means to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law.

You will be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing to use the Service, so please review it frequently. You can see when this policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this policy.

**15\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us by sending an email at pubg_privacy@pubg.com or by writing us at 6, 7, 8F 12, Seocho-daero 38-gil Seocho-gu, Seoul, the Republic of Korea. You can also contact our Data Protection Officer by sending an email at DPO@pubg.com.
